<strings>
	<string control="Core_chkShowGenresText">If enabled, the value of the genre images will always be displayed. If disabled, the text will only be visible when you hover your mouse over one of the genre images.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSourceFromFolder">If enabled, Ember will check the folder name for source types. If disabled, Ember will only check the file name.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkNoDisplayFanart">If enabled, fanart will not be displayed in the main window. This is helpful to speed up the interface on slow computers.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkNoDisplayPoster">If enabled, posters will not be displayed in the main window. This is helpful to speed up the interface on slow computers.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowDims">If enabled, the dimensions of the images (posters and fanart) will be overlayed on top of the images.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkUpdates">If enabled, Ember will check for a new version at each start up.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkOverwriteNfo">Marcada faz com que os arquivos NFOs fora do padrão sejam sobrescritos quando o Ember buscar as informações dos filmes. Desmarcada faz com que os arquivos NFOs não sejam sobrescritos e um novo arquivo, com a extensão .INFO, seja criado.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkLogErrors">If enabled, all errors will be logged to a file located in &lt;Ember Installation Directory&gt;\Log\errlog.txt.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbEpTheme">Select the theme to apply for the episode layout.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbTVShowTheme">Select the theme to apply for the TV Show and Season layout.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbMovieTheme">Select the theme to apply for the movie layout.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnDLTrans">Download addons for Ember, including modules, themes, translations to other languages, and export templates.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbIntLang">Select the language to use for Ember's interface. (You must restart Ember for changes to take effect)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanFolderJPG">Clean all files named "folder.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanExtrathumbs">Clean all "extrathumbs" folders.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanMovieTBN">Clean all files named "movie.tbn".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanMovieNameJPG">Clean all files named &lt;movie&gt;.jpg.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanMovieTBNb">Clean all files named &lt;movie&gt;.tbn.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanMovieJPG">Clean all files named "movie.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanFanartJPG">Clean all files named "fanart.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanPosterJPG">Clean all files named "poster.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanMovieFanartJPG">Clean all files named &lt;movie&gt;-fanart.jpg.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanPosterTBN">Clean all files named "poster.tbn".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanMovieNFO">Clean all files named "movie.nfo".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanDotFanartJPG">Clean all files named &lt;movie&gt;.fanart.jpg.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanMovieNFOb">Clean all files named &lt;movie&gt;.nfo.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkWhitelistVideo">Automatically whitelist all files which have an extension in the "Valid Video Extensions" list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnRemoveWhitelist">Remove the selected extension from the whitelist.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnAddWhitelist">Add the entered extension to the whitelist.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtWhitelist">Enter an extension to add to the whitelist.</string>
	<string control="Core_lstWhitelist">This list contains all the current extensions that will be skipped during cleaning.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkYAMJCompatibleSets">If enabled, Ember will save sets information in a format that is compatible with YAMJ. If disabled, Ember will save sets information in a format that is compatible with XBMC.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkAskCheckboxScrape">If enabled, when clicking on a checkbox in the movies list a non-automatic will be used. If disabled, an automatic scrape will be used.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMarkNew">If enabled, new movies will be "marked". If disabled, new movies will still be colored green until updated or the next Ember session.</string>
	<string control="Core_lbGenre">Select the language(s) of the genres you would like Ember to display.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtCheckTitleTol">Enter the tolerance level you would like Ember to use when title matching. The higher the number, the more lenient the algorithm is. 0 = disabled</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCheckTitles">Enable this to have Ember check the differences between the title of the movie and it's file name. This is useful to make sure that the scraped data is actually for the selected movie file.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnRemoveToken">Remove the selected sort token from the list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnAddToken">Add the entered sort token to the list.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtSortToken">Enter in a sort token to add to the list.</string>
	<string control="Core_lstSortTokens">A list of all current sort tokens. (If the movie title begins with a sort token, then the sort token will be moved to the end. For example: Sort Token = "The", Title = "The Dark Knight", Result = "Dark Knight, The")</string>
	<string control="Core_chkDisplayYear">If enabled, Ember will display the year of the movie in the main movie list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieExtraCol">Hide the Extrathumbs column from the main movie list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieSubCol">Hide the Subtitles column from the main movie list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieTrailerCol">Hide the Trailers column from the main movie list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieInfoCol">Hide the Info column from the main movie list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieFanartCol">Hide the Fanart column from the main movie list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMoviePosterCol">Hide the Poster column from the main movie list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieNameMultiOnly">If enabled, "&lt;movie&gt;.ext" items will only be utilized in folders that have multiple movies. This is useful when you have a mixture of multiple movie and single movie folders and you wish to reduce the number of extra files.</string>
	<string control="Core_rbBracketTrailer">Save trailer files as "&lt;movie&gt;[trailer].ext".</string>
	<string control="Core_rbDashTrailer">Save trailer files as "&lt;movie&gt;-trailer.ext".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkVideoTSParent">If enabled, Ember will save the meta files in the parent directory (YAMJ compatible). If disabled, Ember will save the meta files directly to the VIDEO_TS folder (XBMC compatible). This setting applies to BDMV folders, as well.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieNameNFO">Save nfo files as "&lt;movie&gt;.nfo".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieNFO">Save nfo files as "movie.nfo".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieNameDotFanartJPG">Save fanart files as "&lt;movie&gt;.fanart.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieNameFanartJPG">Save fanart files as "&lt;movie&gt;-fanart.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkFanartJPG">Save fanart files as "fanart.jpg"</string>
	<string control="Core_chkFolderJPG">Save poster files as "folder.jpg"</string>
	<string control="Core_chkPosterJPG">Save poster files as "poster.jpg"</string>
	<string control="Core_chkPosterTBN">Save poster files as "poster.tbn"</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieNameJPG">Save poster files as "&lt;movie&gt;.jpg"</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieJPG">Save poster files as "movie.jpg"</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieNameTBN">Save poster files as "&lt;movie&gt;.tbn"</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMovieTBN">Save poster files as "movie.tbn"</string>
	<string control="Core_lvMovies">The list of all current movie sources. (Paths that will be scanned for movie files)</string>
	<string control="Core_colID">The list of all current movie sources. (Paths that will be scanned for movie files)</string>
	<string control="Core_colName">The list of all current movie sources. (Paths that will be scanned for movie files)</string>
	<string control="Core_colPath">The list of all current movie sources. (Paths that will be scanned for movie files)</string>
	<string control="Core_colRecur">The list of all current movie sources. (Paths that will be scanned for movie files)</string>
	<string control="Core_colFolder">The list of all current movie sources. (Paths that will be scanned for movie files)</string>
	<string control="Core_colSingle">The list of all current movie sources. (Paths that will be scanned for movie files)</string>
	<string control="Core_btnMovieRem">Remove the selected source(s) from the sources list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnMovieAddFolder">Add a new folder to the sources list.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtPosterWidth">Resize poster files to the entered width.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtPosterHeight">Resize poster files to the entered height.</string>
	<string control="Core_tbPosterQual">Adjust the quality of the poster files. (0 = original quality)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkResizePoster">Resize poster files before saving.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbPosterSize">Select the preferred poster size you would like to retreive from the image servers. During automatic scrapers, Ember will attempt to find a poster of this size first. If a poster of the selected size cannot be found, the first available image will be used instead.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkOverwritePoster">If enabled, existing poster files will be overwritten if new ones are selected. If disabled, poster files will only be saved if a current one does not already exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtFanartWidth">Resize fanart files to the entered width.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtFanartHeight">Resize fanart files to the entered height.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkFanartOnly">If enabled, Ember will only retrieve fanart of the selected size. (NOTE: If there are no fanart images of the selected size available, no fanart images will be retrieved)</string>
	<string control="Core_tbFanartQual">Adjust the quality of the fanart files. (0 = original quality)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkResizeFanart">Resize fanart files before saving.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbFanartSize">Select the preferred fanart size you would like to retrieve from the image servers. Durint automatic scrapers, Ember will attempt to find a fanart image of this size first. If a fanart image of the selected size cannot be found, the first available image will be used instead.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkOverwriteFanart">If enabled, existing fanart files will be overwritten if new ones are selected. If disabled, fanart files will only be saved if a current one does not already exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkNoSaveImagesToNfo">If enabled, Ember will not save URLs to the poster and fanart images in the nfo files. (Recommended for YAMJ compatibility)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSingleScrapeImages">Select images while scraping a single movie file.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkUseImgCacheUpdaters">Save images to the image cache when scraping multiple movie files.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkPersistImgCache">If enabled, Ember will not clear the image cache between sessions.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkUseImgCache">Enable Ember's image cache.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkUseETasFA">If enabled and no fanart is available for the selected movie, Ember will use one of the extracted thumbnails as the fanart image.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkNoSpoilers">If enabled, extrathumbs will only be extracted from the first half of the movie in order to avoid "spoilers".</string>
	<string control="Core_txtAutoThumbs">Enter the number of extrathumbs you would like to automatically generate.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkAutoThumbs">If enabled, Ember will automatically extract the entered number of extrathumbs during scraping.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtProxyDomain">Enter the domain for your proxy. (Optional - not necessary for most proxies)</string>
	<string control="Core_txtProxyPassword">Enter the password needed to access your proxy.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtProxyUsername">Enter the username needed to access your proxy.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEnableCredentials">Enable if your proxy requires authentication.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtProxyPort">Enter the port needed to access your proxy.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtProxyURI">Enter the IP or URL needed to access your proxy.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEnableProxy">If enabled, Ember will use the entered proxy for all internet communications.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnDown">Move the selected filter up in the list. (Filters are processed in order from top to bottom)</string>
	<string control="Core_btnUp">Move the selected filter down in the list. (Filters are processed in order from top to bottom)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkProperCase">Automatically apply proper casing to movie titles. (Example: "the dark knight" becomes "The Dark Knight")</string>
	<string control="Core_btnRemoveFilter">Remove the selected filter from the list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnAddFilter">Add the entered filter to the list.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtFilter">Enter text or regex to use as a filter. Special: "a[->]b" = replace all occurrances of "a" with "b" (Example: ".[->]_" will replace all periods in the title with underscores.)</string>
	<string control="Core_lstFilters">The list of all current filters that will be used when generating titles for movies.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMissingExtra">If enabled, Ember will display movies missing extrathumbs when utilizing the Missing Items Filter.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMissingSubs">If enabled, Ember will display movies missing subtitle files when utilizing the Missing Items Filter.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMissingTrailer">If enabled, Ember will display movies missing trailers when utilizing the Missing Items Filter.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMissingNFO">If enabled, Ember will display movies missing nfo files when utilizing the Missing Items Filter.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMissingFanart">If enabled, Ember will display movies missing fanart when utilizing the Missing Items Filter.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMissingPoster">If enabled, Ember will display movies missing posters when utilizing the Missing Items Filter.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkAutoBD">If enabled, Ember will automatically save new fanart images to the entered backdrops folder.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnBrowse">Open a folder browser to select a backdrops folder.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtBDPath">The path to the backdrops folder.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnRemoveNoStack">Remove the selected extension from the No Stack Extensions list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnAddNoStack">Add the entered extension to the No Stack Extensions list.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtNoStack">Enter an extension to add to the No Stack Extensions list.</string>
	<string control="Core_lstNoStack">The list of extensions Ember will not stack into single files when adding them to the library.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnRemMovieExt">Remove the selected extension from the Valid Video Extensions list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnAddMovieExt">Add the entered extension to the Valid Video Extensions list.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtMovieExt">Enter an extension to add to the Valid Video Extensions list.</string>
	<string control="Core_lstMovieExts">The list of extensions Ember will look for when updating the library.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnEditSource">Edit the selected source.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScanOrderModify">If enabled, Ember will add new files in order of there last modified time. If disabled, Ember will add new files to the library in alphabetical order.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSortBeforeScan">If enabled, Ember will sort all single files in the top directory of the source into their own folders.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkIgnoreLastScan">If enabled, Ember will scan all folders/files regardless of the last scan time. If disabled, Ember will only scan files/folders added after the last time files were scanned.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCleanDB">If enabled, Ember will clean the movie database after each scan. (Remove entries for files that no longer exist or no longer match selected setting values)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkAutoDetectVTS">If enabled, Ember will attempt to recognize VIDEO_TS folders even if the folder is not named "VIDEO_TS". If disabled, Ember will still handle VIDEO_TS folders if the folder is named "VIDEO_TS". This setting also applies to BDMV folders.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSkipStackedSizeCheck">If enabled, Ember will not skip files smaller than the entered "Skip Files Smaller Than" size if they contain stacking markers (such as "CD1" or "DVD2").</string>
	<string control="Core_txtSkipLessThan">Ember will use the entered size as the minimum size for movie files. Any files smaller than this will be skipped when updating the library.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtTVSkipLessThan">Ember will use the entered size as the minimum size for episode files. Any files smaller than this will be skipped when updating the library.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbTrailerQuality">Select the preferred quality of the downloaded trailers.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkDeleteAllTrailers">If enabled, Ember will delete all existing trailers for the movie before saving the new one.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkOverwriteTrailer">If enabled, existing trailer files will be overwritten when saving new ones. If disabled, new trailer files will only be saved if one does not already exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkNoDLTrailer">If enabled, trailer files will not be downloaded. Instead, the trailer url will be saved to the nfo.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSingleScrapeTrailer">If enabled, trailers will be downloaded while scraping a single movie.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkUpdaterTrailer">If enabled, trailers will be downloaded during "All Items" scrapers.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkDownloadTrailer">Enable Ember's trailer support.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkAutoETSize">Select the size of the fanart you would like to download as extrathumbs.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbAutoETSize">If enabled, Ember will automatically download all fanart of the selected size as extrathumbs.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtETWidth">Resize extrathumbs to the entered width.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtETHeight">Resize extrathumbs to the entered height.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkETPadding">If enabled, Ember will add "black bars" to the edges of the extrathumbs if they are smaller than the entered size.</string>
	<string control="Core_rbETCustom">Resize extrathumbs to the entered size, regardless of the native resolution.</string>
	<string control="Core_rbETNative">Save extrathumbs using the same resolution as the video.</string>
	<string control="Core_lvTVSources">The list of all current TV Show sources. (Paths that will be scanned for TV Show files)</string>
	<string control="Core_ColumnHeader1">The list of all current TV Show sources. (Paths that will be scanned for TV Show files)</string>
	<string control="Core_ColumnHeader2">The list of all current TV Show sources. (Paths that will be scanned for TV Show files)</string>
	<string control="Core_ColumnHeader3">The list of all current TV Show sources. (Paths that will be scanned for TV Show files)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkTVScanOrderModify">If enabled, Ember will add new files in order of there last modified time. If disabled, Ember will add new files to the library in alphabetical order.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkTVIgnoreLastScan">If enabled, Ember will scan all folders/files regardless of the last scan time. If disabled, Ember will only scan files/folders added after the last time files were scanned.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkTVCleanDB">If enabled, Ember will clean the TV Show database after each scan. (Remove entries for files that no longer exist or no longer match selected setting values)</string>
	<string control="Core_btnAddTVSource">Add a new folder to the sources list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnEditTVSource">Edit the selected source.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnRemTVSource">Remove the selected source(s) from the sources list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonAllJPG">Save All Seasons poster files as "season-all.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonAllTBN">Save All Seasons poster files as "season-all.tbn".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEpisodeDotFanart">Save episode fanart files as "&lt;episode&gt;.fanart.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEpisodeDashFanart">Save episode fanart files as "&lt;episode&gt;-fanart.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEpisodeJPG">Save episode poster files as "&lt;episode&gt;.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEpisodeTBN">Save episode poster files as "&lt;episode&gt;.tbn".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonDotFanart">Save season fanart files as "&lt;season&gt;.fanart.jpg". (Will only save inside the season directory, if it exists)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonDashFanart">Save season fanart files as "&lt;season&gt;-fanart.jpg". (Will only save inside the season directory, if it exists)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonFanartJPG">Save season fanart files as "fanart.jpg". (Will only save inside the season directory, if it exists)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonFolderJPG">Save season fanart files as "folder.jpg". (Will only save inside the season directory, if it exists)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonNameJPG">Save season poster files as "&lt;season&gt;.jpg". (Will only save inside the season directory, if it exists)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonNameTBN">Save season poster files as "&lt;season&gt;.tbn". (Will only save inside the season directory, if it exists)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonPosterJPG">Save season poster files as "poster.jpg". (Will only save inside the season directory, if it exists)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonPosterTBN">Save season poster files as "poster.tbn". (Will only save inside the season directory, if it exists)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonXTBN">Save season poster files as "seasonX.tbn". (Example: season2.tbn)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonXXTBN">Save season poster files as "seasonXX.tbn". (Example: season02.tbn)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowDotFanart">Save show fanart files as "&lt;show&gt;.fanart.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowDashFanart">Save show fanart files as "&lt;show&gt;-fanart.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowFanartJPG">Save show fanart files as "fanart.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowJPG">Save show poster files as "&lt;show&gt;.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowTBN">Save show poster files as "&lt;show&gt;.tbn".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowPosterJPG">Save show poster files as "poster.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowPosterTBN">Save show poster files as "poster.tbn".</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowFolderJPG">Save show poster files as "folder.jpg".</string>
	<string control="Core_btnAddShowRegex">Add the entered regex to the TV Show Regex list.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtSeasonRegex">Enter the regex to use to detect the season number.</string>
	<string control="Core_cboSeasonRetrieve">Choose if you would like to process the season regex against the directory name or the episode file name.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtEpRegex">Enter the regex to use to detect the episode number.</string>
	<string control="Core_cboEpRetrieve">Choose if you would like to process the episode regex against the directory name, the episode file name, or the results of the season regex.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnEditShowRegex">Edit the selected TV Show regex.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnRemoveShowRegex">Remove the selected TV Show regex from the list.</string>
	<string control="Core_lvShowRegex">The list of current TV Show regex.</string>
	<string control="Core_colRegID">The list of current TV Show regex.</string>
	<string control="Core_colSeason">The list of current TV Show regex.</string>
	<string control="Core_colSeasonApply">The list of current TV Show regex.</string>
	<string control="Core_colEpisode">The list of current TV Show regex.</string>
	<string control="Core_colEpApply">The list of current TV Show regex.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkDisplayMissingEpisodes">If enabled, episodes that are missing from your collection will be displayed in the episode list, but will be colored a light gray.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEpisodeNfoCol">Hide the Info column from the episode list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEpisodeFanartCol">Hide the Fanart column from the episode list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEpisodePosterCol">Hide the Poster column from the episode list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonFanartCol">Hide the Fanart column from the season list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeasonPosterCol">Hide the Poster column from the poster list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowNfoCol">Hide the Info column from the show list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowFanartCol">Hide the Fanart column from the show list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowPosterCol">Hide the Poster column from the show list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkDisplayAllSeason">If enabled, if an All Season poster exists for the selected show, it will be displayed on the right of the interface.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbRatingRegion">Select the region of the ratings you would like to display in the interface.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkNoFilterEpisode">If enabled, Ember will not attempt to filter episode file names for titles and instead will build them from the show name, season, and episode until a proper title has been fetched.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnEpFilterDown">Move the selected filter up in the list. (Filters are processed in order from top to bottom)</string>
	<string control="Core_btnEpFilterUp">Move the selected filter down in the list. (Filters are processed in order from top to bottom)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEpProperCase">Automatically apply proper casing to episode titles. (Example: "stole beer from golfer" becomes "Stole Beer From Golfer")</string>
	<string control="Core_btnRemoveEpFilter">Remove the selected filter from the filter list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnAddEpFilter">Add the entered filter to the filter list.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtEpFilter">Enter a filter to add to the filter list.</string>
	<string control="Core_lstEpFilters">The list of all current filters that will be used when generating titles for episodes.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnShowFilterDown">Move the selected filter up in the list. (Filters are processed in order from top to bottom)</string>
	<string control="Core_btnShowFilterUp">Move the selected filter down in the list. (Filters are processed in order from top to bottom)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowProperCase">Automatically apply proper casing to episode titles. (Example: "my name is earl" becomes "My Name is Earl")</string>
	<string control="Core_btnRemoveShowFilter">Remove the selected filter from the filter list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnAddShowFilter">Add the entered filter to the filter list.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtShowFilter">Enter a filter to add to the filter list.</string>
	<string control="Core_lstShowFilters">The list of all current filters that will be used when generating titles for shows.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkGetEnglishImages">If enabled, all English images will be retrieved, regardless of the selected language.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkOnlyTVImagesLanguage">If enabled, only images for the preferred language will be retrieved.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtShowPosterWidth">Resize show poster files to the entered width.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtShowPosterHeight">Resize show poster files to the entered height.</string>
	<string control="Core_tbShowPosterQual">Adjust the quality of the show poster files. (0 = original quality)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkResizeShowPoster">Resize show poster files before saving.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbShowPosterSize">Select the preferred show poster type you would like to retreive from the image servers. During the show scraper, Ember will attempt to find a poster of this type first. If a poster of the selected size cannot be found, the first available image will be used instead.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkOverwriteShowPoster">If enabled, existing show poster files will be overwritten if new ones are selected. If disabled, show poster files will only be saved if a current one does not already exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtShowFanartWidth">Resize show fanart files to the entered width.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtShowFanartHeight">Resize show fanart files to the entered height.</string>
	<string control="Core_tbShowFanartQual">Adjust the quality of the show fanart files. (0 = original quality)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkResizeShowFanart">Resize show fanart files before saving.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbShowFanartSize">Select the preferred fanart size you would like to retreive from the image servers. During the show scraper, Ember will attempt to find a fanart image of this size first. If a fanart image of the selected size cannot be found, the first available image will be used instead.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkOverwriteShowFanart">If enabled, existing show fanart files will be overwritten if new ones are selected. If disabled, show fanart files will only be saved if a current one does not already exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtSeaPosterWidth">Resize season poster files to the entered width.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtSeaPosterHeight">Resize season poster files to the entered height.</string>
	<string control="Core_tbSeaPosterQual">Adjust the quality of the season poster files. (0 = original quality)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeaResizePoster">Resize season poster files before saving.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbSeaPosterSize">Select the preferred season poster type you would like to retreive from the image servers. During the show scraper, Ember will attempt to find a poster of this type first. If a poster of the selected size cannot be found, the first available image will be used instead.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeaOverwritePoster">If enabled, existing season poster files will be overwritten if new ones are selected. If disabled, season poster files will only be saved if a current one does not already exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtSeaFanartWidth">Resize season fanart files to the entered width.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtSeaFanartHeight">Resize season fanart files to the entered height.</string>
	<string control="Core_tbSeaFanartQual">Adjust the quality of the season fanart files. (0 = original quality)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeaResizeFanart">Resize season fanart files before saving.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbSeaFanartSize">Select the preferred fanart size you would like to retreive from the image servers. During the show scraper, Ember will attempt to find a fanart image of this size first. If a fanart image of the selected size cannot be found, the first available image will be used instead.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkSeaOverwriteFanart">If enabled, existing season fanart files will be overwritten if new ones are selected. If disabled, season fanart files will only be saved if a current one does not already exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtEpPosterWidth">Resize episode poster files to the entered width.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtEpPosterHeight">Resize episode poster files to the entered height.</string>
	<string control="Core_tbEpPosterQual">Adjust the quality of the episode poster files. (0 = original quality)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkResizeEpPoster">Resize episode poster files before saving.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkOverwriteEpPoster">If enabled, existing episode poster files will be overwritten if new ones are selected. If disabled, episode poster files will only be saved if a current one does not already exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtEpFanartWidth">Resize episode fanart files to the entered width.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtEpFanartHeight">Resize episode fanart files to the entered height.</string>
	<string control="Core_tbEpFanartQual">Adjust the quality of the episode fanart files. (0 = original quality)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkResizeEpFanart">Resize episode fanart files before saving.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbEpFanartSize">Select the preferred fanart size you would like to retreive from the image servers. During the show scraper, Ember will attempt to find a fanart image of this size first. If a fanart image of the selected size cannot be found, the first available image will be used instead.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkOverwriteEpFanart">If enabled, existing episode fanart files will be overwritten if new ones are selected. If disabled, episode fanart files will only be saved if a current one does not already exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperShowRating">Enable scraping show rating.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperShowActors">Enable scraping show actors.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperShowStudio">Enable scraping show studios.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperShowPremiered">Enable scraping show premiered date.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperShowEGU">Enable scraping the Episode Guide URL.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperShowMPAA">Enable scraping show MPAA.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperShowPlot">Enable scraping show plot.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperShowGenre">Enable scraping show genre.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperShowTitle">Enable scraping show title.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperEpActors">Enable scraping episode actors.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperEpCredits">Enable scraping episode credits.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperEpDirector">Enable scraping episode directors.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperEpPlot">Enable scraping episode plot.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperEpRating">Enable scraping episode rating.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperEpAired">Enable scraping episode aired date.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperEpTitle">Enable scraping episode title.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperEpEpisode">Enable scraping episode number.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScraperEpSeason">Enable scraping season number.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEpLockTitle">If enabled, the episode title will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEpLockRating">If enabled, the episode rating will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkEpLockPlot">If enabled, the episode plot will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowLockPlot">If enabled, the show plot will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowLockGenre">If enabled, the show genre will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowLockStudio">If enabled, the show studio will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowLockRating">If enabled, the show rating will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkShowLockTitle">If enabled, the show title will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_lstTVMetaData">The list of extensions that have default meta data entries.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtTVDefFIExt">Enter an extension to create a default meta data entry.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnRemoveTVMetaDataFT">Remove the default meta data for the selected extension from the default meta data list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnEditTVMetaDataFT">Edit the default meta data for the selected extension in the default meta data list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnNewTVMetaDataFT">Create default meta data for the entered extension and add the to the default meta data list.</string>
	<string control="Core_cboTVMetaDataOverlay">If the selected language is found in the episode, a special icon indicator will be overlayed on the meta data audio icon.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkTVScanMetaData">If enabled, Ember will scan episode files for meta data.</string>
	<string control="Core_cboTVUpdate">Select the time to wait between updating cached TV information files.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtAPIKey">Enter the TVDB API Key of the media center/player you use. This is not necessary for Ember to function. It is only used when saving the Episode Guide URL to the nfo.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtTVDBMirror">Enter the mirror to use when retrieving information from theTVDB.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnTVLanguageFetch">Click to download all available languages from theTVDB.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbTVLanguage">Select the preferred language to use when downloading show information and images.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCertification">Enable scraping movie certification.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkTop250">Enable scraping movie Top 250 ranking.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCountry">Enable scraping movie production country.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtGenreLimit">Limit the number of scraped genres to the entered value.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtActorLimit">Limit the number of scraped actors to the entered value.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCrew">Enable scraping movie other crew. (Scrape Full Crew must be enabled)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMusicBy">Enable scraping movie musicians. (Scrape Full Crew must be enabled)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkProducers">Enable scraping movie producers. (Scrape Full Crew must be enabled)</string>
	<string control="Core_chkWriters">Enable scraping movie writers.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkStudio">Enable scraping movie studio.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkRuntime">Enable scraping movie runtime.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkPlot">Enable scraping movie plot.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkOutline">Enable scraping movie outline.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkGenre">Enable scraping movie genre.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkDirector">Enable scraping movie director.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkTagline">Enable scraping movie tagline.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCast">Enable scraping movie cast.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkVotes">Enable scraping movie votes.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkTrailer">Enable scraping movie trailer url.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkRating">Enable scraping movie rating.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkRelease">Enable scraping movie release date.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMPAA">Enable scraping movie MPAA.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkYear">Enable scraping movie year.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkTitle">Enable scraping movie title.</string>
	<string control="Core_lstMetaData">The list of extensions that have default meta data entries.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtDefFIExt">Enter an extension to create a default meta data entry.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnRemoveMetaDataFT">Remove the default meta data for the selected extension from the default meta data list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnEditMetaDataFT">Edit the default meta data for the selected extension in the default meta data list.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnNewMetaDataFT">Create default meta data for the entered extension and add the to the default meta data list.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkIFOScan">If enabled, Ember will process *.ifo files for meta data information.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbLanguages">If the selected language is found in the movie, a special icon indicator will be overlayed on the meta data audio icon.</string>
	<string control="Core_txtRuntimeFormat">Enter the format you wish to use for the movie duration retrieved from scanning meta data. Note you can also use &lt;0m&gt; for 0 padding minutes</string>
	<string control="Core_chkScanMediaInfo">If enabled, Ember will scan movie files for meta data.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkUseMIDuration">Use the movie duration retrieved from scanning meta data as the runtime of the movie.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkLockOutline">If enabled, the movie outline will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkLockPlot">If enabled, the movie plot will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkLockTrailer">If enabled, the URL movie trailer will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkLockGenre">If enabled, the movie genre will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkLockRealStudio">If enabled, the movie studio will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkLockRating">If enabled, the movie rating will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkLockTagline">If enabled, the movie tagline will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkLockTitle">If enabled, the movie title will only be scraped if a current one does not exist.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbForce">Select the region of the title you would like Ember to look for.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkForceTitle">If enabled, Ember will check for alternative titles in the selected language. This is useful for fetching titles in your native language when scraping foreign films.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkOutlineForPlot">If enabled, Ember will use the outline for the plot if the plot is empty.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCastWithImg">If enabled, Ember will only scrape cast entries that have valid images.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkUseCertForMPAA">If enabled, Ember will use the certifcation of the selected region in place of the MPAA rating.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkFullCast">If enabled, all cast members will be scraped instead of only top billed.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkFullCrew">If enabled, all crew members will be scraped (if individually enabled).</string>
	<string control="Core_cbCert">Select the region to filter certification ratings.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkCert">Only scrape the certificaton rating for the selected region.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMarkNewShows">If enabled, new shows will be "marked". If disabled, new shows will still be colored green until updated or the next Ember session.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkMarkNewEpisodes">If enabled, new episodes will be "marked". If disabled, new episodes will still be colored green until updated or the next Ember session.</string>
	<string control="Core_cbOrdering">Select the default ordering Ember will use when scraping information for a show.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkOnlyValueForCert">If enabled, Ember will only save the value of the certification to the MPAA field. (Example: "Germany:18" will save as "18")</string>
	<string control="Core_rbBanner">If enabled, Ember will attempt to download a banner (wide) image of the selected type as the default show poster.</string>
	<string control="Core_rbPoster">If enabled, Ember will attempt to download a poster image of the selected type as the default show poster.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnResetShowFilters">This will reset the show filters to the default list. WARNING: This WILL delete any custom filters you have entered.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnResetEpFilter">This will reset the episode filters to the default list. WARNING: This WILL delete any custom filters you have entered.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnResetMovieFilters">This will reset the movie filters to the default list. WARNING: This WILL delete any custom filters you have entered.</string>
	<string control="Core_btnResetValidExts">This will reset the valid extensions to the default list. WARNING: This WILL delete any custom extensions you have entered.</string>
	<string control="Core_ResetShowRegex">This will reset the show regex to the default list. WARNING: This WILL delete any custom regex you have entered.</string>
	<string control="Core_chkClickScrape">Enable Click Scrape on main screen column marks.</string>
</strings>